momentum.co.za 2011-06-21

# Momentum Group - Home

Site Usage > Privacy Policy

Momentum and its employees respect your privacy and the protection of your personal information is of the utmost importance to us. In the interests of ensuring that users of this website are adequately protected when supplying personal information, Momentum voluntarily subscribes to the principles outlined in Section 51 of the Electronic Communications and Transactions Act [ECTA] under its Privacy Policy.

## Momentum's privacy policy:

  * Your personal information will not be collected, collated, processed or disclosed by Momentum without your express written consent, unless Momentum is legally required to do so.
  * Your personal information will only be electronically requested, collected, collated, processed or stored by Momentum if it is lawful for us to do so.
  * Should your personal information be required, Momentum will disclose to you in writing the specific purpose for which it is needed. Furthermore, Momentum will not disclose your personal information for any purpose other than the one disclosed to you, nor will it disclose any of your personal information to a third party without your express written consent, unless it is required of us by law.
  * Momentum will keep a record of your personal information and the purpose for which it was used.
  * Momentum will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is kept confidential and secure by storing it on our secure database.
  * Momentum keeps all financial information that it records strictly confidential and will not disclose it to any third party that has no right or title to the information.
  * Momentum will endeavour to take all reasonable and necessary precautions to secure access to your transactions - however, it cannot guarantee the confidentiality of your transactions.
  * Your use of this website is solely at your own risk.
  * Momentum will not be held liable for any personal information that you disclose to a third party whose link may be found on this website. Ensure that you refer to that third party’s privacy policy before you disclose any of your personal information.
  * The Momentum website may make use of cookie and tracking technology, whereby information that you send whilst on the site, is saved on your hard drive and the Momentum website will know who you are when you next visit. This technology is useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, for tracking the number of visitors to a site and understanding how visitors use the website. Personal information cannot be collected via cookie technology.
  * Momentum may use your information for marketing purposes within Momentum and may send you promotional material or details that it thinks may be of interest to you. You will however always be given the opportunity to instruct us to refrain from doing so and to have us remove your details from our mailing list.

This privacy policy may be amended from time to time without any notice to you. Use of this website by you will at any time automatically bind you to the privacy policy that is current at that moment.

Last updated 29 July 2010 17:47
